http://www.aramark.com/other/privacy-policy

Shop
Give your employees the perks that help them recharge and boost their productivity.
Find Refreshments
A professional look delivered to your door, helping your employees look their best.
Rent Uniforms
Create an identity as unique as your business with a diverse range of workwear.
Buy Uniforms
Purchase an array of quality products for incarcerated friends and family members.
SERVICES
We have the safety, food, facilities, and uniforms expertise that lets you focus on what you do best.
INDUSTRIES
We create experiences that matter where people work, learn, recover and play.
Overview
EducationColleges & UniversitiesK-12 Schools & DistrictsHealthcareHospitals & Healthcare FacilitiesSports & EntertainmentStadiums, Arenas & AmphitheatersDestinations & Cultural AttractionsBusiness & GovernmentWorkplaces & Manufacturing FacilitiesConvention CentersConference CentersCorrectional FacilitiesRemote Workplaces
ABOUT US
We deliver an impact wherever people work, learn, recover and play.
Overview
Nourish BlogNews and ResourcesHistoryOur DifferenceLeadershipMedia KitInvestor Relations
SUSTAINABILITY
Sustainability is fundamental to everything we do and guides our everyday actions.
Overview
People
Planet
CAREERS
As an Aramark Service Star, you’ll be able to make an impact on your career, customers and community.
Overview
Career Areas
Why Aramark
Additional Resources
Hourly Employee Resource Center
Search Jobs
Search
Shop
Give your employees the perks that help them recharge and boost their productivity.
Find Refreshments
A professional look delivered to your door, helping your employees look their best.
Rent Uniforms
Create an identity as unique as your business with a diverse range of workwear.
Buy Uniforms
Purchase an array of quality products for incarcerated friends and family members.
Purchase iCare
SELECT YOUR COUNTRY
NORTH AMERICA
United States
Canada
Mexico
SOUTH AMERICA
Argentina
Aramark U.S. Privacy Policy Scope
Aramark (also “we,” “us,” or “our”) offers a broad range of services designed to suit the diverse and ever changing needs of our clients. In order to perform and tailor our services, we collect certain personal information. We take privacy very seriously, and we want you to know how we collect, use, share, and protect information about you and how you can exercise your privacy rights. By interacting with Aramark through our websites, technologies, products and services, you consent to the use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this “Privacy Policy.”
This Privacy Policy applies to our businesses within the United States of America, and provides an overview of our practices across all of our U.S. service offerings. Aramark may also provide supplemental privacy notices to you at specific points where we collect information about you in order to provide additional details about our practices that are applicable to specific products, services and locations.  You should read this Privacy Policy in conjunction with such additional privacy notices. Aramark also maintains some additional privacy policies that are specific to lines of business or to address specific legal requirements. In all cases, this Privacy Policy is subject to applicable law.
This Privacy Policy only applies to personal information that Aramark collects. Please be aware that, in connection with your interactions with Aramark, you may at times share information directly with third parties.  For example, you may access a third-party website through a link from Aramark, you may interact with one of our clients or partners in conjunction with our services, or you may communicate with us through a third-party platform. In these circumstances, Aramark does not have control over what information such third party may collect about you or how that information is used or shared. To learn about how a third party collects, uses, and shares your information, and how to exercise your privacy rights with respect to such third-party processing, please review such third party’s privacy notice.
For California residents, please click here for more information about your California privacy rights.
Types of Information We Collect
When you interact with Aramark, we may collect certain information about you. Please see the chart below to understand what information we collect, the sources of that information, how and why we will use that information, and the potential other recipients of that information. As noted above, we may provide additional details to you about how we collect, use and share your information at the time of collection (for example, at the time you choose to take a consumer survey that we administer).
Category of Personal Information Collected
Source of Information
Purpose for Collection
Categories of Recipients
“Identifying Information”, such as your name, mailing address, email address, and telephone number.
We may collect Identifying Information from you when you visit and use our websites and other technology, order our products or services, communicate with us by mail, phone or email, and/or fill out requests for information through our advertisements, surveys or promotions. We also may receive Identifying Information from third parties that are authorized to provide us with such information.
We use Identifying Information to better serve our customers by making their interactions with us more relevant and enjoyable. We do so by responding to and fulfilling your requests, improving our services, customizing your interactions with us, and communicating with you for marketing and other purposes. For example, we may use Identifying Information to provide you with special offers, notify you of new products, provide customer service, and follow up with you regarding your needs and requests. See the “How to opt-out” section below for more information about how to opt out of such promotional and marketing materials.
We may share Identifying Information with third party service providers to help us achieve the purposes outlined in the previous column. Identifying Information may be shared or combined between affiliates, partners, or other related entities of Aramark for internal business and marketing/promotional purposes. Identifying information, including mailing lists, may also be shared by Aramark with other third parties for their marketing/promotional purposes. See the “Additional Ways We May Share Information About You” section below for more information.
“Payment and Order Information”, such as shipping and billing addresses, and credit and debit card number.
We may collect Payment and Order Information when you make a purchase from us or one of our partners through our websites or other technology, or at the physical locations where we operate.
We use the Payment and Order Information to fulfill your purchases, specifically for shipping and billing.
We may share Payment and Order Information with third party services providers to help us achieve the purposes outlined in the previous column.
“Device Information”, related to your interactions with us, such as device information, geo-location, browser type and operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a unique number that identifies your internet access), cookie information, pages viewed and accessed (including those viewed before and after interacting with our websites), how long you accessed our websites and other technology in any given session, and the date and time of access.
We may collect Device Information automatically when you visit our websites or other technology, or otherwise interact with us. See below for more information on cookies and other technologies used by Aramark.
We use Device Information to ensure that our technology works properly, that you can see and use our intended functionality, and that our technology is secure.  We also may use Device Information for analytics and marketing purposes.
We may share Device Information with third party service providers to help us achieve the purposes outlined in the previous column. See the “The Use of Web Technology” section below for more information.
“Demographic Information”, such as age, gender, geography, etc.
We may collect Demographic Information that you choose to provide to us when you create profiles, participate in promotions, surveys, and otherwise interact with us.  We also may receive Demographic Information from third parties that are authorized to provide us with such information.
We use Demographic Information to improve our services, and offer our customers a more customized experience. When we use Demographic Information it is generally aggregated and anonymized.
We may share Demographic Information with third party service providers to help us achieve the purposes outlined in the previous column.  These third parties may also use this information for the same purposes. When we share Demographic Information it is generally aggregated and anonymized.
“User Preferences”, such as food preferences, dietary restrictions and related information, purchasing preferences, sizes, favorite locations, and preferred hours to receive services.
We may collect User Preferences when you make purchases through us, interact with our websites and other technology, and you choose to provide it to us through surveys or other interactions or communications with us. We also may receive User Preferences from third parties that are authorized to provide us with such information.
We use User Preferences to improve our services, address customer requests, and offer customers a more customized experience. For example, we may use this information to determine the most desirable hours of operation or our locations, to suggest products to you that we think you may like, and to understand what products and services to offer. When we use Demographic Information it is generally aggregated and anonymized.
We may share User Preferences with third party service providers to help us achieve the purposes outlined in the previous column. These third parties may also use this information for the same purposes. When we share User Preferences it is generally aggregated and anonymized.
“Visitor Past Purchases”
We collect Visitor Past Purchase information from the purchases made from us and third parties providing services on our behalf. We also may receive such information from third parties that are authorized to provide us with such information.
We may use Visitor Past Purchase information to improve our services, address customer requests, and offer customers a more customized experience. For example, we may use this information to be certain that we are offering the right products at the right time, and to understand ordering trends by region of the country, what products are the most popular, and generally how our business is doing. We also use Visitor Past Purchase information to offer our customers more customized offerings, for marketing purposes. When we use this information it is generally aggregated and anonymized.
We may share Visitor Past Purchase information with third party service providers to help us achieve the purposes outlined in the previous column. These third parties may also use this information for the same purposes. When we share Visitor Past Purchases information it is generally aggregated and anonymized.
“Survey, Marketing and Promotional Information”, such as contact information—including name, email address, mailing address—and other information you provide in response to surveys, marketing and promotional surveys and campaigns.
Provided by you, at your choice, via electronic or print surveys, questionnaires, or other means.
Survey, Marketing and Promotional Information is used to request more information in relation to the survey or as otherwise permitted under this Privacy Policy. We may also use Survey, Marketing and Promotional Information to improve our services and provide a better experience for you.
We may share Survey, Marketing and Promotional Information with third party service providers to help us achieve the purposes outlined in the previous column.
Additional Ways We May Share Information About You:
In addition to the sharing of your personal information as described above, we also may disclose personal information we collect as follows:
In Connection with Business Transfers:
In the event that all or part of Aramark (such as a line of business or a division) is bought by, sold to or otherwise transferred or distributed to one or more third parties, or is in the process of a potential transaction, customer information will likely be shared for evaluation purposes and included among the transferred business assets.
To Comply with Laws:
Aramark may also disclose information about you when such disclosure appears necessary to comply with the law, a subpoena or other litigation process or to protect the interests or safety of Aramark’s employees, clients, customers or others.
The Use of Web Technology
When you visit our websites and other platforms, we use various web technologies to collect information about how and when you interact with such websites and platforms. The web technologies we use may include cookies, web beacons, and third-party analytics.
Cookies
Cookies are small data files that our websites will generate which will include information you provide to us and information about how you use our websites. This data file will then be retained by your web browser or device to help us better tailor your experience on our sites each time you visit. These cookies will contain different information about you depending upon the types of cookies that are in use.
Types of Cookies We Use
Strictly Necessary—These cookies are used for the essential functions of our websites. For example, they allow us to keep any products or services you plan to purchase in a virtual shopping cart until you are ready to check-out.
Performance Cookies—These cookies allow us to view broad categories of information regarding who comes to our websites. This information is used to improve our website functionality and does not contain identifying information about you.
Functionality Cookies—These cookies allow us to customize your experience on our websites by storing your preferences and other information you provide to us. These are cookies designed to remember information you provide such as your preferred language, region, and, if you choose, your log-in information so that you can be automatically logged-in.
Advertising Cookies—These cookies are used to customize what ads you might see on our websites or ads from us on other websites. This information allows us to better tailor our offerings to you either through ads more appropriate to your needs, or to prevent repeated ads that you may not want.
If you do not want cookies, you can set your computer or other device to warn you each time a cookie is being set or turn off all cookies through your browser (e.g., Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox). Check your browser HELP menu to learn the way to change or update your cookies. However, it is possible that some parts of our websites will not operate correctly if you disable cookies; therefore, by doing so, you may not be able to take advantage of some of the website features. Note that browser-management tools for cookies are outside of our control and we cannot guarantee their effectiveness. Certain websites may have automated tools to allow you to turn off or update your cookies, and in such instance you could use such automated tools to manage your cookie preferences.
Although cookies are not necessary to view Aramark's websites or receive advertisements from us, cookies may be required to place an online order. Should you wish to not accept cookies in your web browser, you may place an order by calling the phone numbers listed on the applicable Contact Us pages on our websites.
Web Beacons
In addition to cookies, we may include web beacons on our websites. Web beacons are small transparent images (sometimes called “clear gifs”) that will let us know when you visit our websites and which links on our websites you visit. This information is helpful to know which sites are accessed so that we can improve your experience each time you visit. The web beacons we use do not collect any personally identifiable information. We can use this anonymous information to make it easier to understand what you are looking for.
Third Party Analytics
We may also use third-party analytics software such as Google Analytics for our own internal purposes including evaluating how you use our websites. The third party services may use cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about your use and to report on activities and trends. Such services may also collect information regarding your use of other websites, applications, and online resources. For more information about Google Analytics, please go to www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You may download the Google Analytics opt out browser add-on at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Offers and Promotions
At times, we may conduct offers and marketing campaigns (collectively “Customer Events”). Some of these Customer Events may involve mailing catalogs, coupons, SMS texts, or other forms of communication from us to you. These Customer Events will be directed toward visitors of our websites, individuals from lists we receive from third parties, or individuals that opt-in to a Customer Event. Some Customer Events may require you to opt-in in a manner that meets all legal requirements.  Please see the “How Can I Opt-Out” section for more information about how to opt-out of Customer Events.
Sweepstakes and Other Promotions
In addition to Customer Events we provide, there may be times where you can opt into one of our sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions (collectively “Sweepstakes”). These Sweepstakes may ask for personal information such as contact information (name, email address, mailing address, etc.). Participation in our Sweepstakes is optional. If you choose to participate in our Sweepstakes, we may use and share the information you provide with our affiliates to administer the sweepstakes.
Affiliate Programs
At times, Aramark may affiliate with a third-party to provide offers, promotions, or operate a rewards program (collectively “Affiliate Programs”). These Affiliate Programs may be offered on our websites, technology or at any of our physical locations. When you provide information in connection with these Affiliate Programs, you may be providing it directly to one or more third-party affiliates and its usage will be subject to that third party’s privacy notice.  While our use, collection, storage, and sharing of your information will be governed by this Privacy Policy, for information on how the third-party affiliates collect, use, store, and share your data please see their individual privacy policies. In addition, for any data collected in our physical locations please see the available privacy policies at the respective points of collection for more information.
How Your Information Is Stored and Retained
At Aramark, we take the security, confidentiality, and integrity of your information very seriously. We utilize technical, physical, and administrative safeguards that are designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, retrieval, disclosure, use, and modification. If we transmit, share, or use your information we take appropriate methods to prevent from any interception or unauthorized access to that data.
We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you products and services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
How Can I Opt-Out?
If you would like to opt-out of any of our promotional offerings or marketing campaigns, please email us at Privacy@aramark.com. After verifying your identity, we will take appropriate measures to remove you from our marketing lists in compliance with applicable law. In addition, you may opt-out of such promotional and marketing campaigns by clicking the opt-out link at the bottom of the applicable digital marketing or advertising communications.
How this Privacy Policy May Change
From time to time, we may update this notice to accommodate changes in how you interact with us, address changes in the law, or for any other purpose. We will maintain a “LAST UPDATED” date at the top of this notice to show when any changes are made. Any changes we make to this notice will be effective as of the date at the top of this notice.
Information about Minors
Aramark does not target its websites or any of its services or products to children and does not knowingly collect personal information from children under thirteen (13) years of age. If Aramark learns that a child under the age of thirteen (13) has submitted personal information on Aramark’s websites without parental consent, Aramark will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from our databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required or allowed by law). If you become aware of any personal information we have collected from children under thirteen (13), please contact us using at Privacy@aramark.com.
Minors under eighteen (18) years of age may email us at Privacy@aramark.com to have the personal information they have provided to us deleted, subject to applicable law.  Please note that, while we make reasonable efforts to comply with such requests, deletion of your personal information does not ensure complete and comprehensive removal of that data from all systems.
Information for California Residents - Your California Privacy Rights
The California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) grants certain rights to California residents to access or delete the personal information that we have collected about them, to opt-out of the sale of their personal information by us to a third party, and not to be discriminated against for exercising these rights.
Access
California residents have the right to request what personal information we collected, used, disclosed, and sold about them within the preceding 12 months. Once we receive your request and confirm your identity and California resident status, we will disclose to you the information that we have collected about you, as required by the CCPA.
Deletion
California residents have the right to request the deletion of their personal information that we collect or maintain. Once we receive your request and confirm your identity and California resident status, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies. Such exceptions include, but are not limited to, when the personal information is necessary to complete a transaction or provide goods or services to you, detect security incidents, comply with the law, and for internal uses reasonably aligned with your expectations.
Opt-Out
California law requires us to identify, for the 12-month period prior to the date of this Privacy Policy, what information Aramark has "sold" about you, and you have a right to opt-out of such sale.  We do not sell any personal information of minors under the age of 16 without receiving affirmative authorization to do so. Also, generally speaking, please be assured that Aramark does not sell or rent your information to third parties purely for our profit, to data brokers, or in any way other than those intended to improve your online experiences and the relevance of offers made to you through Aramark’s websites and elsewhere.  There are instances where Aramark has shared personal information in order to provide our customers with personalized services or customized offers to improve your online experiences, and to improve our products and services.  We do this in ways that are intended to extend the Aramark experience to our customers in a variety of environments. Depending on the circumstances and the contractual obligations in place, this sharing may be a "sale" under applicable law and you may have the right to request that we stop such sharing as more fully set forth below. This sharing includes:
Identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, geolocation information, unique personal identifier (such as a device identifier; cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers and similar technology; customer number, unique pseudonym, or user alias; telephone number and other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers), online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, and other similar identifiers;
commercial information, including records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, and other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies;
Internet and other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with Aramark’s websites, applications or advertisements; and
inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, predispositions, and behavior.
Non-Discrimination
California Residents have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment if and when they exercise their rights to access, delete, or opt-out under the CCPA.
This means we cannot, for example:
Deny goods or services to you;
Charge different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or by imposing penalties;
Provide a different level or quality of goods or services to you; or
Suggest that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
Please note that we may charge a different price or rate, or provide a different level or quality of goods and/or services to you, if that difference is reasonably related to the value provided to you by your personal information.
Exercising Your Rights
In order to exercise your “access”, “deletion”, and/or “opt-out” rights, you may submit a request through a web form here or call us at (877) 999-4862.  You may also authorize another person (your "agent") to submit a request on your behalf, and in the same manner.  Once we receive your request, we will contact you to verify your identity and California resident status and review your request.
We aim to respond to your requests within 45 days of receiving the request. If we need more time to respond to your request, we will let you know the reason and how much additional time we will need.
California- Direct Marketing information
Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (the "Shine The Light" law), customers who are California residents and have a relationship with Aramark primarily for personal, family, or household purposes are entitled to receive, upon request and free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year. This information may be requested once a year. If applicable, this information will include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of the third parties that received the information. If you are a California resident and want to make a request for this information, please submit your request in writing to: Privacy@aramark.com or Aramark, 2400 Market Street, Philadelphia, PA 19103 Attn: Assistant General Counsel Privacy (please reference the "Shine The Light Law" in your email or letter).
Privacy Policy for California Residents
Under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, California users are entitled to the following consumer rights notice: If you have a question or complaint regarding the websites, please send an e-mail to Privacy@aramark.com. You may also contact us by writing to Aramark, 2400 Market Street, Philadelphia, PA 19103, Attn: VP, Compliance, Privacy or by calling us at (800) 388-3300. California residents may reach the Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs by mail at 1625 North Market Blvd., Sacramento, CA 95834, or by telephone at (916) 445-1254 or (800) 952-5210.
Do Not Track Signals
Do Not Track is a standard that is currently under development. As it is not yet finalized, we adhere to the standards set out in this Privacy Policy and do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals except as may be required by law.
How Can You Contact Aramark
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or to request a copy of this Privacy Policy in another format,  please contact us at the following:
Mail: 2400 Market Street,
Philadelphia PA 19103
Attn: VP, Compliance
(800) 388-3300
Email: Privacy@aramark.com
ABOUT ARAMARK
Aramark (NYSE: ARMK) is in the customer service business across food, facilities and uniforms, wherever people work, learn, recover, and play. United by a passion to serve, our 280,000 team members deliver experiences that enrich and nourish the lives of millions of people in 19 countries around the world every day.
Home
Contact Us
Terms & Conditions
U.S. Privacy Policy
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
Sitemap
ServicesFood ServicesFacilities ServicesUniform ServicesIndustriesColleges & UniversitiesK-12 Schools & DistrictsHospitals & Healthcare FacilitiesStadiums, Arenas & AmphitheatersDestinations & Cultural AttractionsWorkplaces & Manufacturing FacilitiesConvention CentersConference CentersCorrectional FacilitiesRemote WorkplacesAbout UsNourish BlogNews and ResourcesHistoryOur DifferenceLeadershipMedia KitInvestor RelationsCareersCareer AreasWhy AramarkAdditional ResourcesUniform Services Opportunities
Awards
